

Krishna K. Keshri

MERN DEVELOPER

+91-8553192768

Arrah, Bihar

keshri819@gmail.com

krishna-keshri.vercel.app

in @krishna-kumar-keshri

@KrishnaKumarKeshri96

PROFILE

Passion-driven learner and a web developer with the ability to write clean, reusable and optimized code. Skilled and experienced at building and maintaining MERN based web applications. Looking forward to working in a challenging and progressive work environment.

SKILLS

- Javascript
- ReactJS
- Redux
- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- MongoDB
- Data Structures & Algorithms

EDUCATION HISTORY

MERN Stack Web Development

Masai School 04/2021 - 09/2021 | Online

Bachelor of Hotel Management

Ramaiah University 2014 – 2018 | Bangalore

PROJECTS

Cult.fit clone 🔿 🔗

Build clone of fitness megastore platform Cultfit using MERN stack as a part of learning curve in Masai School.

Features:

- End-to-end product purchasing flow from the store.
- Buying subscription and booking a demo workout session from cult.fit.
- Integrated with the backend using MongoDB

Tech Stack: CSS | React | Node | Express | MongoDB **Areas of responsibility:**

- Developed the cult.fit membership subscription flow. and a store page.
- Contributed to integrating the database and logic for the users and products

A collaborative project, built in 5 days by a team of 4 developers and 2 designers.

Internshala Clone 👩 🔗

A clone of Internshala which is an online platform that lists internships and training programs.

Features:

- Sign-in/sign-up
- Filters for internships, search bar.
- Dynamic view details page.

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | Javascript | Node | Express | MongoDB **Areas of responsibility:**

- Developed the Sign-in/Sign-up pages
- Laid out database schema and build the REST API for the same.
- Developed the dynamic 'view details' page

A collaborative project built by a team of 3, executed in 4 days.

Covid-Stats \right 🤌

An overview of the damage caused by Covid-19 in the form of maps and charts.

Features:

- Select country by clicking on map
- Sort by Number of cases country-wise
- Decent UI

Tech Stack: SCSS| React

An individual one-day project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INSTRUCTIONAL ASSOCIATE | DEVELOPER

Masai School

Oct 2021 - Present

- Led daily stand-ups for students where I would guide students with academics by clarifying the conceptual doubts.
- Assisted teaching staffs with assignment supervision and administered project completion for the group.
- Organized and recommended technical sessions when required.
- Worked on internal projects.

ASSISTANT RESTAURANT MANAGER

KFC - Bengaluru

2018 - 2021

- To set high standards for appropriate team behavior on shift.
- To maintain budget and employee records, check payroll, pay bills, and monitor records.
- Manage daily restaurant operations and assist with product planning, forecasting, maintain sanitation standards and plan labor hours.